<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Notes on Coderhacks</title>
    <link>http://coderhack.com/notes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Notes on Coderhacks</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2017 11:27:27 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://coderhack.com/notes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Autonomous Car: Advanced lane detection</title>
      <link>http://coderhack.com/notes/advanced-lane-detection/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2017 11:27:27 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://coderhack.com/notes/advanced-lane-detection/</guid>
      <description>The goals / steps of this project are the following:
 Compute the camera calibration matrix and distortion coefficients given a set of chessboard images. Apply a distortion correction to raw images. Use color transforms, gradients, etc., to create a thresholded binary image. Apply a perspective transform to rectify binary image (&amp;ldquo;birds-eye view&amp;rdquo;). Detect lane pixels and fit to find the lane boundary. Determine the curvature of the lane and vehicle position with respect to center.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ESP 8266 based water controller</title>
      <link>http://coderhack.com/notes/home-automation-iot-node-red/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2017 18:29:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://coderhack.com/notes/home-automation-iot-node-red/</guid>
      <description>Home automation series part 1 As summers are nearing, wanted to go on vacation, now that I have couple of plants that need to be watered when I am on the move.. thought its a good usecase to be automated.
One option is to have timer which can switch on a valve once in a day, however due to power interruption It might loose track unless I build a battery backup for the controller.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docker getting started</title>
      <link>http://coderhack.com/notes/docker-getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://coderhack.com/notes/docker-getting-started/</guid>
      <description>Docker experiment to build hello world image from scratch. Instead of using shell script, C based application is used to make it comparable to custom application package/distribution.
 Creating minimal docker image what you need :
 docker installed on linux variant (tested on Ubuntu 14LTS)
 gcc for making minimal application
  docker can import archives such as tar, tar.gz, .bzip etc. you can package all necessary files into an archive and import it into docker.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>